Joseph Le

647.770.0975

@

joseph.le14@gmail.com

•••

josephle.xyz



56 Port Royal Trail Scarborough, ON

Education

OCAD University

2010 – 2014 Bachelor's Degree, Graphic Design

Awards / Honors

Summer Company Youth Entrepreneurship Program

Summer 2013 Youth Entrepreneur / Award Recipient

Professional Skills

Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Indesign
HTML & CSS (Basic)
Copywriting
Strategic Branding
Conceptual UI/UX Design
Editorial Design
Illustration
Multidisciplinary Collaboration

References

Available upon request

Overview

I am a visual designer with experience working on digital, print, and brand strategy. My passion for design is centered around creating pragmatic, user-centric, and compelling research-driven narratives.

I am capable of working independently and also excel in collaborative team settings.

Experience

Navigator Ltd.

Graphic Designer

- Facilitated the design of presentation decks (RFPs, clients) and other project deliverables with quick turnaround times
- · Ensured that products were consistent with brand guidelines
- Worked on the redesign of the Navigator website by developing sketches, site maps, user flows, and wireframes

Pakathon Global

Graphic Designer

- Collaborated with a multidisciplinary, global team to consolidate and build a more cohesive visual identity for the organization
- Produced design solutions that generated further interest for the Toronto event; increased participant numbers from 50 to 100+
- Designed web graphics, promotional prints, presentations for corporate fundraising, and a social media campaign

Health in Motion Rehabilitation

Graphic Designer / Web Marketing

- Developed layouts and oversaw production for newsletters, brochures, online publications, and social media content
- Managed the company's branding and online presence through their social media channels

Freelance Projects

Boost: Equity Crowdfunding Portal

Visual + UX/UI Designer

- Served as visual lead on design from conception; created iterative wireframes, high-fidelity mockups, and an early prototype
- Worked closely with developers to create a functional MVP prototype of the web platform
- Conducted extensive user testing through 50+ user interviews and 250+ user surveys: increased conversion rate by 30% during alpha testing

Jan 2016 - Present

Aug 2014 - Jan 2016

Sept 2014 - Feb 2015

July 2014 - Sept 2015